pickjack.com 2013-04-04

# Pickjack.com , Privacy Policy

**Overview**

This Privacy Policy sets forth the policies of PickJack LLC ("PJLLC") with respect to nonpublic information you provide to us through the web site PickJack.com (the "Site"). These policies may be changed at any time, in which case the revised Privacy Policy will apply to information collected after the date the Privacy Policy is posted. By accessing the Site, you agree that you have read and understand the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

**Our Policy**

We recognize the value of your privacy and appreciate concerns you may have about information you provide to us when you visit us online and how we treat that information. We encourage you to read this entire Privacy Policy as it sets forth our policies with respect to personal information you provide us through our Site. Other privacy practices may apply to information you provide to us through other channels. "Personal Identifiable Information" refers to information that allows us to identify you, such as your name, address, zip/postal codes, telephone number, organization name if applicable, e-mail address, etc.   
We are committed to safeguarding your privacy and upholding the highest levels of information security. To that end, we adhere to the strictest consumer privacy guidelines and use special care in order to protect any personal information you provide through the Site.   
Users with questions or concerns regarding their privacy or this statement should contact PJLLC Customer Service at:   
**E-mail:[support@pickjack.com](mailto:support@pickjack.com)**

**Information Collection**

We will never sell, rent, loan or otherwise distribute any of your Personal Identifiable Information (including your name, e-mail address, phone number or any other identifiable information about you) to any third party without your prior expressed written consent, other than to our affiliates, as permitted by law, such as to our attorneys, auditors, and to certain service providers, such as a third party that hosts this Site, but, in all such cases, only as necessary to facilitate the acceptance and management of our Site (i.e., passing certain information on to PayPal in which to pay you). We will also release information about you if you direct us to do so, if compelled to do so by law or in connection with any government or self-regulatory organization request or investigation.

From time to time, PJLLC may use aggregate data collected through the Site to analyze website usability, system performance and usage trends. While this data, in its aggregate form only, may be shared with third parties with whom PJLLC works to analyze it, the data will only be shared under the strictest terms of confidentiality and will never contain any Personally Identifiable Information pertaining to any user of the Site. 

****
  1. **What We Collect**

When you browse through our Site we collect: 

    * Basic information about your computer, browser and connection to make sure that we can give you proper information and customer service and for security purposes.
    * Aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit to improve our site.
    * All information voluntarily submitted by users (relating to profiles, questions and answers, comments, and point bidding). If you choose to register to become a member of our site ("Member"), which by becoming a Member enables you to post information and earn points (the "Services"), we will ask you for more information, including the following:
    * Your e-mail address so we can contact you and pay you;
    * Your date of birth which, among other things, ensures that all of our users are of legal age and provides us with general demographic information; and
    * A login and password that enables you to update your personal information on our Site at any time in the future.
If you choose sell your points it will be necessary that the email address you have on file is connected to a PayPal account. 
  2. ****

**Changing and Updating Personal Information; Choosing Options:**

You may change any of your personal account information by going to the "My Account" page and clicking the "Edit Account Info" button. You may change your e-mail address, password, as well as your privacy settings. We will also give you the option to choose whether you would like to receive e-mail from PJLLC. If you would like to receive these solicitations, simply check the appropriate box. You can choose to stop participating at any time simply by using the following methods: 

    1. changing your preferences on the Site; 
    2. replying to an e-mail's "unsubscribe" function 

**Profile**

We store information that we collect through cookies and log files to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users' Personally Identifiable Information to provide offers and improve the content of the Site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Site. This information may also be used to help improve our overall services. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any 

**Personally Identifiable Information you submit while on our Site.**  
**A. Cookies:**  
A "cookie" is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is not linked to any Personally Identifiable Information while a user is visiting our Site. We use both "session cookies" and "persistent cookies". For the "session cookie," once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A "persistent cookie" is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still browse our site, but they will not be able to buy or sell reservations. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

**B. Log Files:**  
Like most standard website servers, we use "log files". Log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring pages, platform type, date/time stamp. IP addresses, etc. are linked to Personally Identifiable Information. We use log files in error diagnostics, session management and in determining our advertising efficacy. Communications from the Site 

**A. Transactions and Service Announcements:**  
Members who register on the site will receive a number of e-mails throughout the transaction process and they may sometimes receive phone calls from our Customer Service department to ensure smooth transactions. We may also occasionally send out service-related announcements (e.g., if our Services are temporarily suspended for maintenance). These communications are not promotional in nature, and users will receive them as long as their accounts are open. 

**B. Special Offers, Newsletters and Updates:**   
Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications, as explained in the Choice and opt-out section below. 

**C. Customer Service:**  
We will communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services. We respond to issues relating to a user's account via e-mail or telephone, in accordance with each user's preference. 

**D. Choice and opt-out:**  
A user can change their opt-in or opt-out status in the following ways: 

  1. From a Newsletter/E-mail: Click on the "Unsubscribe" link within the e-mail. The next step is to select the alerts which you no longer wish to receive and click the "unsubscribe" button. If the Site does recognize you, you do not have to enter your e-mail address. Simply select the alerts which you no longer wish to receive and click the "unsubscribe" button. 
  2. From the Site: If you have a username and password, log into your account by clicking the Login link on the home page. Then click the "My Account" link on the top navigation bar. Once in My Account, you can then update your alerts within "My Preferences." In the "Contact Preferences" section, you can revise your alerts preferences by adding or removing checks from the radio buttons in "My PickJack" alerts section. Then click the "Save" button. Testimonials and Photo Usage

If you submit testimonials, photos, blogs, writings, customer satisfaction surveys or other writings or media ("Voluntarily Submitted Media") in connection with use of our Site and the Services, you thereby grant PJLLC the perpetual right to use any public information on your account in connection with PJLLC's marketing and publicity efforts in any and all media and you thereby agree to release any rights or claims you may have against PJLLC with respect to PJLLC's use of such Voluntarily Submitted Media. Said media shall include, without limitation, print, radio, television, internet, e-mail, magazine and any other form of communication whether now known or hereafter devised.

No consideration is being paid for this release, and you hereby and acknowledge and understand that PJLLC is relying on this release without consideration if it avails itself of any or all of the rights granted herein. 

**Sharing Information**

We may share your personal information with third parties in the following instances: **Within Our Corporate Family:**  
We may share information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures or other companies under common control, where it may be used to provide joint services or for purposes such as internal statistics, strategic decision-making, customer verification, fraud prevention and security. 

**Legal Disclaimer:**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may disclose personal information when required by law or under the good-faith belief that such action is necessary under applicable law. We may disclose personal information in order to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We also share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, to protect our property or interests or that of our agents and employees, and to protect personal safety or the public. 

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable):**

We share some aggregated demographic information (age, zip codes) with some of our partners. This is not linked to any Personally Identifiable Information. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. 

**Third Party Service Providers:**  
We may disclose information about individual users to third parties who provide services to PJLLC. These third parties provide a variety of services to PJLLC, including, without limitation, verifying credit card information, fulfilling orders via courier delivery, processing credit card transactions, and disbursing payments to sellers. In addition, these services may include enhancing the information PJLLC collects about its customers. 

**Business Transitions:**  
In the event PJLLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, an acquisition by another company, or a sale of all or a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via prominent notice on our Site for 30 days after a change of ownership or control of their personal information, if personal information will be used contrary to this policy. If as a result of the business transition, the users' Personally Identifiable Information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, users will be given the option to continue sharing their information consistent with our notification of changes section. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to interfere with the ability of PJLLC to transfer all or part of its business and/or assets (including the Site), for any purposes, without any limitation whatsoever. PJLLC specifically reserves the right to transfer or share a copy of Personally Identifiable Information collected from its Site to the buyer of that portion of its business relating to that information. 

**External Links**  
The Site contains links to other websites maintained by third parties. Please be aware that PJLLC exercises no control over linked sites and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. Each linked site maintains its own independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures, and you are encouraged to view the privacy policies of these other sites before providing any personal information. 

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by e-mail, or by means of a notice on our home page.
